5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tA-Save")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Academy")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_translate"))
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_bita-farming"))
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_01.md"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_A FARMER represents God, and the VINEYA_8b10d9"))
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/div_A FARMER represents God,edit box"), " test edit by the test script")
45. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Save"))
49. delay(2)
53. if (verifyElementNotClickable(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Save"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("
Save button is greyed out as expected")
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/Chip_English - unfoldingWorden_taElsyLambert-tc-create-1"))
61. delay(2)
65. switchToWindowIndex(1)
69. if (getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/h4_dcs article")).contains("test edit by the test script"))
1. logInfo("
The edits are saved on the DCS Repo File")
73. switchToWindowIndex(0)
77. logInfo("
TEST PASSED:Edits are saved successfully in tA articles")
81. closeBrowser()
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())