9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Organization unfoldingWord"))
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Translation Notes"))
21. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_Step 4 Select Your Language option am -_f1dc08"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input_Step4Select Your Language_react-selec_aae5da"), "en")
29. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/div_en - English - English (Europe Gateway)"))
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
37. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""test"")
41. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""on"")
45. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Literal Text v14"), 5))
2. logInfo("Cannot find ULT in PSV")
49. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Simplified Text v14"), 5))
2. logInfo("Cannot find UST in PSV")
53. logInfo("ParallelScripture is present")