1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Parallel Scripture Viewer")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
29. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""test"")
33. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""on"")
37. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Literal Text v14"), 5))
2. logInfo("Cannot find ULT in PSV")
41. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Simplified Text v14"), 5))
2. logInfo("Cannot find UST in PSV")
45. logInfo("ParallelScripture is present")
49. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""off"")
53. logInfo("button is toggled")