5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Highlighting by occurrence number")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_view columns"))
33. click(findTestObject("tN objects/input_OrigQuote_checkbox"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/input_SupportReference"))
41. click(findTestObject("tN objects/button__Close-Columns"))
45. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
49. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
53. delay(1)
57. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
61. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/div_Titus 11"), 2)
65. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_add a new row"))
69. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Add"))
73. word1 = getText(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"))
77. logInfo("the word is" + word1)
81. color_word1 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"), "color")
85. backcolor_word1 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"), "background-color")
89. logInfo(color_word1)
93. logInfo(backcolor_word1)
97. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_OL_box"))
101. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_OL_box"), "Θεοῦ")
105. driver = getWebDriver()
109. action = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(driver)
113. build().perform()
117. if (!(color_word1.equals(backcolor_word1)))
2. logInfo("First Occurrence is not highlighted! or No hightlight at all!")
121. color_word2 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word2"), "color")
125. backcolor_word2 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word2"), "background-color")
129. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"))
133. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
137. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), "2")
141. build().perform()
145. if (!(color_word2.equals(backcolor_word2)))
2. logInfo("Text is not highlighted!")
149. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
153. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), "-1")
157. build().perform()
161. if (!(color_word1.equals(backcolor_word1)) && !(color_word2.equals(backcolor_word2)))
2. logInfo("Text is not highlighted!")
165. delay(2)
169. closeBrowser()
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())