5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables())
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Add new resource")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"), 1)
29. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
33. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
37. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
41. delay(1)
45. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
49. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_TIT 1intro"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
53. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_Titus 11"))
57. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_Titus 11"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
61. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Manage Versions"))
65. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"))
69. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"), "Door43-Catalog/hi/ulb/master/")
73. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Add_Resource Path"))
77. if (verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_unfoldingWord Simplified Textv14_jss5689"), 1))
2. logInfo("Resource unchecked")
81. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Manage Versions"))
85. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"))
89. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"), "https://git.door43.org/ru_gl/ru_rlob")
93. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Add_Resource Path"))
97. if (verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_unfoldingWord Simplified Text-Russian check box"), 1))
2. logInfo("Resource unchecked")
101. delay(2)
105. try
1. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Hamburger Menu Button"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
109. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_01-GEN.tsv"))
113. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/button_DrawerClose"))
117. delay(1)
121. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_GEN frontintro"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("Other Books which do not have the added resource did not crash ")
125. closeBrowser()
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())