1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Parallel Scripture Viewer")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. delay(2)
29. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"), 1)
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
37. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""test"")
41. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""on"")
45. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Literal Text v14"), 5))
2. logInfo("Cannot find ULT in PSV")
49. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Simplified Text v14"), 5))
2. logInfo("Cannot find UST in PSV")
53. logInfo("ParallelScripture is present")
57. com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture(""off"")
61. logInfo("button is toggled")
65. if (verifyElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Literal Text v14"), 3))
1. logInfo("ULT is not visible as expected")
69. closeBrowser()
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())