9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
29. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
33. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
37. delay(1)
41. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
45. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_TIT 1intro"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_Expand chapter button"))
53. mouseOver(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/td_12"))
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/td_12"))
61. for (int i : (1..18))
1. sendKeys(findTestObject(null), Keys.chord(PAGE_DOWN))
65. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/sup_315")))
2. logInfo("Chapter not expanded")
69. delay(3)
73. sendKeys(findTestObject(null), Keys.chord(PAGE_UP))
77. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_collapse-chapter"))
81. delay(2)
85. if (verifyElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/sup_315"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("Chapter is collapsed successfully")
89. closeBrowser()
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Highlighting by occurrence number")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()