9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Academy")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_translate"))
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_bita-farming"))
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_01.md"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/button_Sections"))
41. if (verifyElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/div_A FARMER represents God, collapse tab"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("Collapsable Sections are not visible and is expanded as expected
")
45. if (getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/div_My well beloved had a vineyard")).contains("My well beloved had a vineyard"))
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("OBS-tQ-Save")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()