17. KeywordUtil.logInfo("Execution profile is " + executionProfile)
1. callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC tsv Open For Edit"), ["$username":"", "$password":"", "file":""], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (binding.hasVariable("file") && file.contains(".tsv"))
2. myFile = tNFile
5. println("tsv file is " + myFile)
9. if (binding.hasVariable("language"))
2. myLanguage = ""
13. println("language is " + myLanguage)
17. if (binding.hasVariable("organization"))
2. myOrg = ""
21. println("language is " + myLanguage)
25. if (binding.hasVariable("resource"))
2. myResource = "/en_tn"
29. println("language is " + myLanguage)
33. callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC Login"), ["user":$username, "password":$password, "newSession":true], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (newSession)
1. if (openBrowser)
1. openBrowser("")
5. maximizeWindow()
5. println("Opening " + url)
9. navigateToUrl(url)
13. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/text_tCCVersion"), 30)
17. version = getText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/text_tCCVersion"))
21. version = version
25. println("Version is " + version)
5. if (user == "")
1. println("Logging in as " + user1Name)
5. activeUser = user1Name
9. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input__username"), user1Name)
13. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input__password"), user1Password)
17. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Login"), 1, OPTIONAL))
1. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Login"))
37. if (callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC Select Org-Lang-Resource"), ["organization":myOrg, "language":myLanguage, "file":myFile, "resource":myResource], STOP_ON_FAILURE) == false)
1. if (binding.hasVariable("resource"))
1. myResource = resource
5. println("resource is " + myResource)
9. if (organization == "")
1. organization = organization
13. if (language == "")
1. language = langCode
17. println("Choosing organization " + organization)
21. if (waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/listOrg_Parmed", ["organization":organization]), 5, OPTIONAL) == false)
2. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/listOrg_Parmed", ["organization":organization]))
6. alerted = waitForAlert(2)
10. if (alerted == true)
2. println("Not alerted on organization")
6. alertFlag = false
10. if (myResource instanceof java.util.List)
2. listFlag = false
14. if (resource.indexOf("/") == 0)
1. resource = resource.substring(1, resource.length())
18. rsrc = "unfoldingWord/" + resource
22. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/resource_Parmed", ["resource":rsrc]), 1, OPTIONAL))
1. resource = rsrc
26. println("Choosing resource " + resource)
30. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/resource_Parmed", ["resource":resource]))
34. println("Choosing language " + language)
38. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/combo_Select Language"))
42. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/listOption_Language_Parmed", ["lang_code":language]))
46. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.checkBranchAlert()
50. if (listFlag)
14. return true
1. suite = false
5. fileName = testSuiteLogFile
9. if (fileName != null && fileName.length() > 1)
1. suite = true
5. println("test case teardown in suite")
9. println("log file is at " + fileName)
13. browser = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getBrowserAndVersion()
17. separator = "==================================================================================================================================================="
21. msg = separator
25. println(msg)
29. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
33. prefix = " +++++++++++ "
37. testCaseStatus = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
41. if (scriptRunning)
45. if (testCaseStatus != "PASSED")
1. prefix = " ---------------------- "
49. executionProfile = getExecutionProfile()
53. msg = prefix + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId() + " on " + version + " running on " + browser + " in " + executionProfile + " " + testCaseStatus + prefix
57. println(msg)
61. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
65. tsMessages.add("##" + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
69. if (scriptRunning)
73. if (tcMessages.size() > 0)
77. if (scriptRunning && 1 == 2)
81. if (testCount > 0)
85. if (timings.size() > 0)
89. msg = separator
93. println(msg)
97. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
1. println("setup start")
5. systemOS = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getOperatingSystem()
9. tcMessages = []
13. executionProfile = getExecutionProfile()