17. KeywordUtil.logInfo("Execution profile is " + executionProfile)
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Expand chapter")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.checkBranchAlert()
29. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
33. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.checkBranchAlert()
37. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
41. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
45. delay(1)
49. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
53. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_TIT 1intro"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_Expand chapter button"))
61. mouseOver(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/td_12"))
65. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/td_12"))
69. for (int i : (1..19))
1. sendKeys(findTestObject(null), Keys.chord(PAGE_DOWN))
73. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/sup_315")))
2. logInfo("Chapter not expanded")
77. delay(3)
81. sendKeys(findTestObject(null), Keys.chord(PAGE_UP))
85. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_collapse-chapter"))
89. delay(2)
93. if (verifyElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/sup_315"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("Chapter is collapsed successfully")
97. closeBrowser()
1. suite = false
5. fileName = testSuiteLogFile
9. if (fileName != null && fileName.length() > 1)
1. suite = true
5. println("test case teardown in suite")
9. println("log file is at " + fileName)
13. browser = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getBrowserAndVersion()
17. separator = "==================================================================================================================================================="
21. msg = separator
25. println(msg)
29. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
33. prefix = " +++++++++++ "
37. testCaseStatus = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
41. if (scriptRunning)
45. if (testCaseStatus != "PASSED")
1. prefix = " ---------------------- "
49. executionProfile = getExecutionProfile()
53. msg = prefix + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId() + " on " + version + " running on " + browser + " in " + executionProfile + " " + testCaseStatus + prefix
57. println(msg)
61. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
65. tsMessages.add("##" + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
69. if (scriptRunning)
73. if (tcMessages.size() > 0)
77. if (scriptRunning && 1 == 2)
81. if (testCount > 0)
85. if (timings.size() > 0)
89. msg = separator
93. println(msg)
97. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
1. println("setup start")
5. systemOS = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getOperatingSystem()
9. tcMessages = []
13. executionProfile = getExecutionProfile()