17. KeywordUtil.logInfo("Execution profile is " + executionProfile)
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Highlighting by occurrence number")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.checkBranchAlert()
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
33. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.checkBranchAlert()
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_view columns"))
41. click(findTestObject("tN objects/input_OrigQuote_checkbox"))
45. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/input_SupportReference"))
49. click(findTestObject("tN objects/button__Close-Columns"))
53. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
57. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
61. delay(1)
65. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
69. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/div_Titus 11"), 2)
73. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_add a new row"))
77. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Add"))
81. word1 = getText(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"))
85. logInfo("the word is" + word1)
89. color_word1 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"), "color")
93. backcolor_word1 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"), "background-color")
97. logInfo(color_word1)
101. logInfo(backcolor_word1)
105. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_OL_box"))
109. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_OL_box"), "Θεοῦ")
113. driver = getWebDriver()
117. action = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(driver)
121. build().perform()
125. if (!(color_word1.equals(backcolor_word1)))
2. logInfo("First Occurrence is not highlighted! or No hightlight at all!")
129. color_word2 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word2"), "color")
133. backcolor_word2 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word2"), "background-color")
137. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"))
141. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
145. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), "2")
149. build().perform()
153. if (!(color_word2.equals(backcolor_word2)))
2. logInfo("Text is not highlighted!")
157. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
161. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), "-1")
165. build().perform()
169. if (!(color_word1.equals(backcolor_word1)) && !(color_word2.equals(backcolor_word2)))
2. logInfo("Text is not highlighted!")
173. delay(2)
177. closeBrowser()
1. suite = false
5. fileName = testSuiteLogFile
9. if (fileName != null && fileName.length() > 1)
1. suite = true
5. println("test case teardown in suite")
9. println("log file is at " + fileName)
13. browser = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getBrowserAndVersion()
17. separator = "==================================================================================================================================================="
21. msg = separator
25. println(msg)
29. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
33. prefix = " +++++++++++ "
37. testCaseStatus = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
41. if (scriptRunning)
45. if (testCaseStatus != "PASSED")
1. prefix = " ---------------------- "
49. executionProfile = getExecutionProfile()
53. msg = prefix + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId() + " on " + version + " running on " + browser + " in " + executionProfile + " " + testCaseStatus + prefix
57. println(msg)
61. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
65. tsMessages.add("##" + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
69. if (scriptRunning)
73. if (tcMessages.size() > 0)
77. if (scriptRunning && 1 == 2)
81. if (testCount > 0)
85. if (timings.size() > 0)
89. msg = separator
93. println(msg)
97. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
1. println("setup start")
5. systemOS = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getOperatingSystem()
9. tcMessages = []
13. executionProfile = getExecutionProfile()