9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_unfoldingWord"))
17. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_unfoldingWord Translation Notes"))
21. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/div_Select Language"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Step4Select Your Language_react-selec_aae5da"), "en")
29. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/div_en - English - English (Europe Gateway)"))
33. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
37. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
41. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
45. delay(1)
49. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
53. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_TIT 1intro"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_Expand chapter button"))
61. mouseOver(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/td_12"))
65. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/td_12"))
69. for (int i : (1..18))
1. sendKeys(findTestObject(null), Keys.chord(PAGE_DOWN))
73. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/sup_315")))
1. logInfo("Chapter is expanded successfully")
77. delay(3)
81. sendKeys(findTestObject(null), Keys.chord(PAGE_UP))
85. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_collapse-chapter"))
89. delay(2)
93. if (verifyElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/sup_315"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("Chapter is collapsed successfully")
97. closeBrowser()
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Highlighting by occurrence number")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()