1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Add new resource")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Translation Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
29. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
33. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
37. delay(1)
41. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
45. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_TIT 1intro"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_Titus 11"))
53. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_Titus 11"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Manage Versions"))
61. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"))
65. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"), "Door43-Catalog/hi/ulb/master/")
69. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Add_Resource Path"))
73. if (verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_unfoldingWord Simplified Textv14_jss5689"), 1))
1. driver = getWebDriver()
5. action = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(driver)
9. build().perform()
13. delay(2)
17. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/Header_Unlocked Literal Bible - Hindi v5"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. out.println("New Resource Header Present in the Scripture Viewer")
5. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/Hindi ULB Text"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo(" New Resource Text added by a Relative path is Present in the Scripture Viewer")
77. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Manage Versions"))
81. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"))
85. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"), "https://git.door43.org/ru_gl/ru_rlob")
89. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Add_Resource Path"))
93. if (verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_unfoldingWord Simplified Text-Russian check box"), 1))
1. driver = getWebDriver()
5. action = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(driver)
9. build().perform()
13. delay(2)
17. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_RLOB v1"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. out.println("New Resource Header Present in the Scripture Viewer")
5. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/div_11-russian text"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo(" New Resource Text added by a URL is Present in the Scripture Viewer")
97. delay(2)
101. try
1. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Hamburger Menu Button"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
2. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/chip_Repo"), 2)
6. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_DrawerOpen"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)