9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Organization unfoldingWord"))
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_unfoldingWord Translation Academyunfold_cb119f"))
21. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/p_Select Language"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/input_Step4Select Your Language_react-selec_aae5da"), "en")
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_en - English - English (Europe Gateway)"))
33. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_translate"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_bita-farming"))
41. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_01.md"))
45. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/button_Sections"))
49. if (verifyElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/div_A FARMER represents God, collapse tab"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("Collapsable Sections are not visible and is expanded as expected
")
53. if (getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/div_My well beloved had a vineyard")).contains("My well beloved had a vineyard"))
1. logInfo("Section is expanded as expected and text is visible
")
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/button_Blocks"))
61. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/button_Preview"))
65. if (getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/block in preview mode")).contains(">"))
1. logInfo("Preview mode is ON as expected
")
69. closeBrowser()