1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("OBS-sn-Save")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()
9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.organization("")
17. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.resource("unfoldingWord® Open Bible Stories Study Notes")
21. com.tccreate.keywords.selectOrg.language("")
25. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/OBS-tn/div_content"))
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/OBS-tn/span_02"))
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/OBS-tn/span_02.md"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/obs-sn/div_a snake edit box"))
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/obs-sn/div_a snake edit box"), "  edits by a test script")
45. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/button_Save"))
49. delay(2)
53. if (verifyElementNotClickable(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Save"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo(" Save button is greyed out as expected")
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/obs-sn/div_English - unfoldingWorden_obs-snElsyLambert-tc-create-1"))
61. delay(2)
65. switchToWindowIndex(1)
69. if (getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/obs-sn/h1_a snake DCS page")).contains("edits by a test script"))
1. logInfo("The edits are saved on the DCS Repo File")
73. switchToWindowIndex(0)
77. closeBrowser()
81. closeBrowser()