9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_unfoldingWord"))
17. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_unfoldingWord Translation Notes"))
21. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/div_Select Language"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Step4Select Your Language_react-selec_aae5da"), "en")
29. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/div_en - English - English (Europe Gateway)"))
33. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
37. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
41. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
45. delay(1)
49. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
53. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_TIT 1intro"), 2, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_Titus 11"))
61. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_Titus 11"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
65. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Manage Versions"))
69. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"))
73. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"), "Door43-Catalog/hi/ulb/master/")
77. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Add_Resource Path"))
81. if (verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_unfoldingWord Simplified Textv14_jss5689"), 1))
1. driver = getWebDriver()
5. action = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(driver)
9. build().perform()
13. delay(2)
17. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/Header_Unlocked Literal Bible - Hindi v5"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. out.println("New Resource Header Present in the Scripture Viewer")
5. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/Hindi ULB Text"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo(" New Resource Text added by a Relative path is Present in the Scripture Viewer")
85. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Manage Versions"))
89. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"))
93. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_Resource Path_resourceUrl"), "https://git.door43.org/ru_gl/ru_rlob")
97. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/button_Add_Resource Path"))
101. if (verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/input_unfoldingWord Simplified Text-Russian check box"), 1))
1. driver = getWebDriver()
5. action = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(driver)
9. build().perform()
13. delay(2)
17. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_RLOB v1"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. out.println("New Resource Header Present in the Scripture Viewer")
5. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/div_11-russian text"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo(" New Resource Text added by a URL is Present in the Scripture Viewer")
105. delay(2)
109. try
1. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Hamburger Menu Button"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
2. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/chip_Repo"), 2)
6. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_DrawerOpen"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
113. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/span_en_tn_01-GEN.tsv"))
117. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/button_DrawerClose"))
121. delay(1)
125. if (verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/Add new resource objects/h6_GEN frontintro"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("Other Books which do not have the added resource did not crash ")
129. closeBrowser()