9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Organization unfoldingWord"))
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_unfoldingWord Translation Notes"))
21. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_Step 4 Select Your Language option am -_f1dc08"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input_Step4Select Your Language_react-selec_aae5da"), "en")
29. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/div_en - English - English (Europe Gateway)"))
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_en_tn_57-TIT.tsv"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_view columns"))
41. click(findTestObject("tN objects/input_OrigQuote_checkbox"))
45. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/input_SupportReference"))
49. click(findTestObject("tN objects/button__Close-Columns"))
53. buttonstate = com.tccreate.keywords.ExpandAllScriptureToggle.toggleAllScripture("test")
57. out.println(" the state of the button is" + buttonstate)
61. delay(1)
65. if (buttonstate == "off")
2. logInfo("Parallel scripture viewer is ON")
69. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/div_Titus 11"), 2)
73. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Titus 11_add a new row"))
77. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/button_Add"))
81. word1 = getText(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"))
85. logInfo("the word is" + word1)
89. color_word1 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"), "color")
93. backcolor_word1 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word1"), "background-color")
97. logInfo(color_word1)
101. logInfo(backcolor_word1)
105. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_OL_box"))
109. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_OL_box"), "Θεοῦ")
113. driver = getWebDriver()
117. action = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(driver)
121. build().perform()
125. if (!(color_word1.equals(backcolor_word1)))
1. logInfo("First Occurrence is highlighted!")
129. color_word2 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word2"), "color")
133. backcolor_word2 = getCSSValue(findTestObject("tN objects/word2"), "background-color")
137. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"))
141. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
145. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), "2")
149. build().perform()
153. if (!(color_word2.equals(backcolor_word2)))
1. logInfo("Second occcurrence is highlighted!")
157. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
161. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tN objects/p_occurrence box"), "-1")
165. build().perform()
169. if (!(color_word1.equals(backcolor_word1)) && !(color_word2.equals(backcolor_word2)))
1. logInfo("Both occurrences are highlighted!")
173. closeBrowser()
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tW-Save")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()