9. com.helper.login.loginhelper.logintoapp()
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/Organization unfoldingWord"))
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_unfoldingWord Translation Academyunfold_cb119f"))
21. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/p_Select Language"))
25. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/input_Step4Select Your Language_react-selec_aae5da"), "en")
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_en - English - English (Europe Gateway)"))
33. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_translate"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_bita-farming"))
41. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/span_01.md"))
45. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_tC Create/div_A FARMER represents God, and the VINEYA_8b10d9"))
49. sendKeys(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/div_A FARMER represents God- Edit box"), " test edit by the test script")
53. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Save"))
57. delay(2)
61. if (verifyElementNotClickable(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Save"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE))
1. logInfo("
Save button is greyed out as expected")
65. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/Chip_English - unfoldingWorden_taElsyLambert-tc-create-1"))
69. delay(2)
73. switchToWindowIndex(1)
77. if (getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/tA/h4_dcs article")).contains("test edit by the test script"))
1. logInfo("
The edits are saved on the DCS Repo File")
81. switchToWindowIndex(0)
85. logInfo("
TEST PASSED:Edits are saved successfully in tA articles")
89. closeBrowser()
1. com.tccreate.keywords.WriteToFile.writeTofilename("tN-Add new resource")
5. com.helper.login.TimeDate.getTimeDate()